

Developer seeking assignment in Software Development, Application
Maintenance, Project Management, Program Mgmt, Requirement Gathering, Business
Analysis, Quality Mgmt, Hybris, Spring Boot, Spring MVC/Core, Core Java, Servlets, JSP,
XML, SQL, Javascript



Current Designation: Senior Associate Technology Total Experience: 6 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Publicis Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Delhi Highest Degree:

Pref. Location: Delhi / NCR

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: senior systems engineer, software development, project management, core java, servlets, jsp, alfresco

activiti,sql,html,javascript,spring,spring boot,SAP,Hibernate,hybris

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: Jul-Sep 2020 Last Modified: Jul-Sep 2020

Summary

Result-oriented Professional with over 3 years of experience in Software Development, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Program Management, Requirement Gathering, Business Analysis, Quality Mgmt, Hybris, SPring, Spring Boot, Core Java, Servlets, JSP, XML, Alfresco Activiti, ,SQL, Adobe Live Cycle

Work Experience

Publicis as Senior Associate Technology May 2020 to Till Date

Leading a team of 2-3 people Hybris CCV2 Implementation Hybris 1905 Migration

Accenture as Application Developer Senior Analyst Mar 2018 to May 2020

Leading a team of 2-3 people Code optimization using coverity tool Unit test case preparation using Mockito framework

Infogain as Consultant Jul 2017 to Mar 2018

- ? Leading a team of 2-3 people
- ? Implemented end to end security for data communication
- ? Implementation of TDE at DB level for security optimization
- ? Code optimization using coverity tool
- ? Unit test case preparation using Mockito framework

Infosys, **Limited** as Senior Systems Engineer -IT Application Jun 2014 to Jul 2017

Development and testing.

Frequent client meetings and demos.

Documentation for client presentations.

Project

Name: eBiz Portal

Client: Department of Industrial Policy and Promotion, Government of India

Duration: November, 2014 - Present

Responsibilities:

Alfresco Activiti

Designing process flows using the Alfresco Activiti 1.3.1.

Creating DB Scripts in SQL to write process-specific data to the database.

Designing request and response XSDs to accommodate client requirements.

Weblogic Portal

Implementing the requirements in java using Oracle Weblogic Workshop 10g.

Developing jsp and incorporate the change requirements.

Developing REST based web services for transfer of data to client.

Spring (MVC)

Developing service specific controllers and implementing flows.

Developing REST based web services for transfer of data to client.

Creating DB scripts in PostgreSQL to write service-specific data to the database.

Adobe Live Cycle

Developing service specific eforms and corresponding XMLs.

Creating XSDs for binding of data to eform.

Creating DB scripts in SQL to write service-specific data to the database.

Business Process Management

Designing process flows using the Oracle BPM Studio 10.3.

Creating DB Scripts in SQL to write process-specific data to the database.

Designing request and response XSDs to accommodate client requirements.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University (GGSIU) in 2014

PG: in 0

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Core Java, Servlets, JSP, XML			
XSD, Alfresco Activiti , BPM , SQL			
Adobe Live Cycle			
HTML, Javascript and CSS			
Eclipse IDE .			
HYBRIS	1.808	2019	1 Year(s) 3 Month(s)
spring boot	2.0	2019	4 Year(s) 7 Month(s)

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak	
English	Proficient				

 $1/22/2021 \hspace{1.5cm} https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=fe5b75a8a2fe548503af55f45069b6445e550b5519460d115119400e5f5... \\$

Hindi Proficient

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary

Employment Status: Full time